A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Family and Friends, Series H FA343
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Reubhausen, Oscar M. - Special Services (Box 17, Folder 211)
- Saarinen, Aline B. (Box 18, Folder 212)
- Sarnoff, General David (Box 18, Folder 213)
- Saunders, Dr. George M. (Box 18, Folder 214)
- Savell, Isabelle (Box 18, Folder 215)
- Scadron, Margot de Vankhier (Box 18, Folder 216)
- Sevilla-Sacasa, Alberto and Guillermo (Box 18, Folder 217)
- Sheets, Harold F. (Box 18, Folder 218)
- Shimamoto, George G. (Box 18, Folder 219)
- Simpson, Marilyn Milton (niece) (Box 18, Folder 220)
- Skouras, Spyros O. (Box 18, Folder 221)
- Smith, G. E. Kidder (Box 18, Folder 222)
- Smith, Mr. and Mrs. Harold D. (Box 18, Folder 223)
- Spaeth, Carl B. (Box 18, Folder 224)
- Spock, Anne (Box 18, Folder 225)
- Sternick, Harry L. (Box 18, Folder 226)
- Stettinius, Edward R., Jr. (Box 18, Folder 227)
- Stott, Frederic A. (Box 18, Folder 228)
- Straus, Jack I. (Box 18, Folder 229)
- Switzer, Mary E. (Box 18, Folder 230)
- Taylor, Wayne C. (Box 18, Folder 231)
- Teller, Dr. Edward (Box 18, Folder 232)
- Thomas, Lowell (Box 18, Folder 233)
- Tomlinson, Edward (Box 18, Folder 234)
- Troy, Walter A. (Box 19, Folder 235)
- Truslow, Mr. and Mrs. Francis Adams (Box 19, Folder 236)
- Tschudy, Arnold (Box 19, Folder 237)
- Tucker, Morrison G. (Box 19, Folder 238)
- Turck, Fenton B. (Box 19, Folder 239)
- Turnbull, Mr. and Mrs. Barton P. (Box 19, Folder 240)
- Uht, Carol K. (Box 19, Folder 241)
- Von Pohle, Dr. Charles L. (Box 19, Folder 242)
- Wallace, Henry A. (Box 19, Folder 243)
- Warren, Earl (Box 19, Folder 244)
- Warren, Fletcher (Box 19, Folder 245)
- Warren, William C. (Box 19, Folder 246)
- Watt, Mr. and Mrs. Robert J., Sr. (Box 19, Folder 247)
- Webb and Knapp, Inc. (Box 19, Folder 248)
- White, John E. (Box 19, Folder 249)
- White, John R. and Laboratory to Integrate Our National Knowledge (LINK) (Box 19, Folder 250)
- White, John R. and Laboratory to Integrate Our National Knowledge (LINK) (Box 19, Folder 251)
- Whitman, Ann C. (Box 20, Folder 252)
- Whitney, H. LeRoy (Box 20, Folder 253)
- Weiss, Olga (Box 20, Folder 254)
- Wise, John (Box 20, Folder 255)
- Zeckendorf, William (Box 20, Folder 256)
- Zeckendorf, William - Godchaux Sugar (Box 20, Folder 257)
- Rockefeller family
  - General Correspondence and Clippings (Box 20, Folder 258)
  - General Correspondence and Clippings (Box 20, Folder 0258A)
  - Contributions (Box 20, Folder 259)
  - Major Philanthropies (Box 20, Folder 260)
  - Rockefeller Memorial Collection Distributions (Box 20, Folder 261)
  - Planes - Wayfarer Ketch (Box 20, Folder 262)
  - Book by E. Tidyman, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 263)
  - Use of Name (Box 20, Folder 264)
  - Cousins Addresses and Articles (Box 21, Folder 265)
  - Cousins Addresses and Articles (Box 21, Folder 0265A)
  - Cousins Office Manual (Box 21, Folder 267)
- William Avery Rockefeller (Box 21, Folder 268)
- John D. Rockefeller Sr.
  - Correspondence (A-K) (Box 21, Folder 269)
  - Correspondence (L-Z) (Box 21, Folder 270)
  - General, 1935-1971 (Box 22, Folder 271)
  - Will - NAR Trustee (Box 22, Folder 272)
  - Property - Michigan Hill (Box 22, Folder 273)
  - Histories (Box 22, Folder 274)
  - Property - Mansion House, Lakewood, New Jersey (Box 22, Folder 275)
  - Property - Casements, Ormond Beach, Florida (Box 22, Folder 276)
- Incoming Personal Correspondence, 1920-1930
  - A, 1920-1930 (Box 22, Folder 277)
  - B, 1920-1930 (Box 22, Folder 278)
  - Jette Lamier Baker, 1920-1930 (Box 22, Folder 279)
  - Pierre Benoit, 1920-1930 (Box 22, Folder 280)
  - Don de Beris, 1920-1930 (Box 22, Folder 281)
  - Helen Rockefeller Bowler, 1920-1930 (Box 22, Folder 282)
  - Barbara (Bobby) Briggs, 1920-1930 (Box 22, Folder 283)
  - Thatcher Brown, Jr., 1920-1930 (Box 23, Folder 284)
  - Tallmadge (Tad) Bullock, 1920-1930 (Box 23, Folder 285)
  - C, 1920-1930 (Box 23, Folder 286)
  - Otis Caldwell, 1920-1930 (Box 23, Folder 287)
  - Geraldine Chittoline, 1920-1930 (Box 23, Folder 288)
  - Catharine (Kittens) B. Clothier, 1920-1930 (Box 23, Folder 289)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Percy Clark, 1920-1930 (Box 23, Folder 290)
  - Percy Clark, Jr., 1920-1930 (Box 23, Folder 291)
  - Clark Family Members, 1920-1930 (Box 23, Folder 292)
  - Mary Todhunter Clark (Rockefeller), 1926-1928 (Box 23, Folder 293)
  - Mary Todhunter Clark (Rockefeller), 1929 (Box 23, Folder 294)
  - Mary Todhunter Clark (Rockefeller), 1930 (Box 23, Folder 295)
  - D, 1920-1930 (Box 24, Folder 296)
  - Dartmouth Friends, 1920-1920 (Box 24, Folder 297)
  - E, 1920-1930 (Box 24, Folder 298)
  - F, 1920-1930 (Box 24, Folder 299)
  - Jane Foster, 1920-1930 (Box 24, Folder 300)
  - Mary Billings French, 1920-1930 (Box 24, Folder 301)
  - Elizabeth French, 1920-1930 (Box 24, Folder 302)
  - Mary French (Rockefeller), 1920-1930 (Box 24, Folder 303)
  - John French, 1920-1930 (Box 24, Folder 304)
  - G, 1920-1930 (Box 24, Folder 305)
  - Lydia Garrison, 1920-1930 (Box 24, Folder 306)
  - Robert W. Gumbel, 1920-1930 (Box 24, Folder 307)
  - Grenfell Expedition, 1929 (Box 24, Folder 308)
  - H, 1920-1930 (Box 24, Folder 309)
  - Charles O. Heydt, 1920-1930 (Box 24, Folder 310)
  - J, 1920-1930 (Box 24, Folder 311)
  - K, 1920-1930 (Box 24, Folder 312)
  - Anna Kelly, 1920-1930 (Box 24, Folder 313)
  - L, 1920-1930 (Box 24, Folder 314)
  - M, 1920-1930 (Box 24, Folder 315)
  - Jacques and Phillipe Marozeau, 1920-1930 (Box 24, Folder 316)
  - Ted Martin, 1920-1930 (Box 24, Folder 317)
  - Adele Merrill, 1920-1930 (Box 24, Folder 318)
  - Alida Millikan, 1920-1930 (Box 24, Folder 319)
  - N, 1920-1930 (Box 25, Folder 320)
  - O, 1920-1930 (Box 25, Folder 321)
  - P, 1920-1930 (Box 25, Folder 322)
  - R, 1920-1930 (Box 25, Folder 323)
  - S, 1920-1930 (Box 25, Folder 324)
  - T, 1920-1930 (Box 25, Folder 325)
  - V, 1920-1930 (Box 25, Folder 326)
  - W, 1920-1930 (Box 25, Folder 327)
  - Anna Wakefield, 1920-1930 (Box 25, Folder 328)
  - "Sis" Watts, 1920-1930 (Box 25, Folder 329)
  - Z, 1920-1930 (Box 25, Folder 330)
  - First Names Only, 1920-1930 (Box 25, Folder 331)
  - Billy, 1920-1930 (Box 25, Folder 332)
  - Wilma, 1920-1930 (Box 25, Folder 333)
- NAR Personal Invoices and Receipts, 1924-1930 (Box 25, Folder 334)
- NAR Bank Statements, 1924-1925 (Box 25, Folder 335)
- NAR Honors Paper on Standard Oil, 1929 (Box 25, Folder 336)
- NAR Engagement Clippings, 1929-1930 (Box 25, Folder 337)
- Miscellaneous Dartmouth Items, 1926-1930 (Box 25, Folder 338)
- School Notebook of Political Cartoons, 1921-1925 (Box 26, Folder 339)
- Journal of Family Vacation, 1920 (Box 26, Folder 340)
- Georgraphy Notebook, early 1920s (Box 26, Folder 341)
- Mixed Miscellaneous Items (Box 26, Folder 342)
- Cards to Abby Aldrich Rockefeller from NAR's Children, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 343)
- Cards to Abby Aldrich Rockefeller from NAR's Children, 1930s-1940s (Box 26, Folder 0343A)
- NAR World Trip (Honeymoon), 1930-1931 (Box 26, Folder 344)
- NAR World Trip (Honeymoon) Brochures, 1930-1931 (Box 26, Folder 345)
- NAR Passport, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 346)
- Miscellaneous Childhood and Dartmouth Photographs, 1920s (Box 27, Folder 347)
- Vachel Lindsay at Dartmouth, 1929 (Box 27, Folder 348)
- Dartmouth Papers and Grades, 1926-1930 (Box 27, Folder 349)
- Miscellaneous Papers, 1908-1926 (Box 27, Folder 350)
- Lincoln School, Senior Yearbook, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 351)
- Miscellaneous Addresses and Contacts, 1920s (Box 27, Folder 352)
- Art Interests, 1920s (Box 27, Folder 353)
- Copies of Letters from Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, 1921-1941 (Box 28, Folder 354)
- Letters from John D. Rockefeller Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, 1917-1920 (Box 28, Folder 355)
- Letters from John D. Rockefeller Jr., Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1921-1922 (Box 28, Folder 356)
- Letters from John D. Rockefeller Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, 1923-1924 (Box 28, Folder 357)
- Letters from John D. Rockefeller Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, 1926 (Box 28, Folder 358)
- Letters from John D. Rockefeller Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, 1927 (Box 28, Folder 359)
- Letters from John D. Rockefeller Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, 1928 (Box 28, Folder 360)
- Letters from John D. Rockefeller Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, 1929 (Box 28, Folder 361)
- Letter from John D. Rockefeller Jr. upon NAR's Engagement, November 15, 1929 (Box 28, Folder 362)
- Letters from John D. Rockefeller Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, 1930 (Box 28, Folder 363)
- Letters from John D. Rockefeller Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, 1931 (Box 28, Folder 364)
- NAR Letters to John D. Rockefeller Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, 1914-1924 (Box 29, Folder 366)
- NAR Envelopes and Calling Cards to Abby Aldrich Rockefeller (Box 29, Folder 367)
- NAR Letters to John D. Rockefeller Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, 1925-1926 (Box 29, Folder 368)
- NAR Letters to John D. Rockefeller Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, 1927 (Box 29, Folder 369)
- NAR Letters to John D. Rockefeller Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, 1928 (Box 29, Folder 370)
- NAR Letters to John D. Rockefeller Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 371)
- NAR Letters to John D. Rockefeller Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, 1930 (Box 30, Folder 372)
- NAR Letters to John D. Rockefeller Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller During World Trip (Honeymoon), 1930-1931 (Box 30, Folder 373)
- NAR Letters to John D. Rockefeller Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, 1931-1933 (Box 30, Folder 374)
- NAR Letters to John D. Rockefeller Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, 1934-1936 (Box 30, Folder 375)
- NAR Letters to John D. Rockefeller Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, 1937, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 376)
- NAR and John D. Rockefeller Jr. Correspondence: JDR Jr. Office File, 1928-1960
  - 1928-1937 (Box 31, Folder 377)
  - 1938-1945 (Box 31, Folder 378)
  - 1946-1953 (Box 31, Folder 379)
  - 1954-1957 (Box 31, Folder 380)
  - 1958-1960 (Box 31, Folder 381)
- NAR and John D. Rockefeller Jr. Correspondence - Pocantico Hills House, 1930-1934 (Box 32, Folder 382)
- NAR and John D. Rockefeller Jr. Correspondence - E. 67th Street Apartment, 1931-1932 (Box 32, Folder 383)
- NAR and John D. Rockefeller Jr. Correspondence - NAR Presents, 1930-1964 (Box 32, Folder 384)
- NAR and John D. Rockefeller Jr. Correspondence - Wedding and World Trip, 1929-1930 (Box 32, Folder 385)
- NAR and John D. Rockefeller Jr. Correspondence - Mary (Tod) Rockefeller Presents, 1930-1939 (Box 32, Folder 386)
- NAR and John D. Rockefeller Jr. Correspondence - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller's Estate, 1948-1950 (Box 32, Folder 387)
- NAR and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Correspondence, 1931-1948 (Box 32, Folder 388)
- NAR Personal Correspondence from John D. Rockefeller Sr., 1919-1923 (Box 32, Folder 389)
- NAR and John D. Rockefeller 3rd Correspondence, 1922-1931 (Box 32, Folder 390)
- Letters from Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1925-1931 (Box 32, Folder 391)
- Letters from Abby (Babs), Winthrop, and David Rockefeller, c. 1925-1931 (Box 32, Folder 392)
- John D. Rockefeller Jr., 1960-1971 (Box 33, Folder 393)
- John D. Rockefeller Jr., 1960-1971 (Box 33, Folder 0393A)
- NAR Correspondence Regarding John D. Rockefeller Jr., 1961-1971 (Box 33, Folder 394)
- NAR Correspondence with John D. Rockefeller Jr., 1931-1934 (Box 33, Folder 395)
- NAR Correspondence with John D. Rockefeller Jr., 1935-1942 (Box 33, Folder 396)
- NAR Correspondence with John D. Rockefeller Jr., 1935-1942 (Box 33, Folder 0396A)
- NAR Correspondence with John D. Rockefeller Jr., 1943-1944 (Box 33, Folder 397)
- NAR Correspondence with John D. Rockefeller Jr., 1945-1946 (Box 33, Folder 398)
- NAR Correspondence with John D. Rockefeller Jr., 1947 (Box 34, Folder 399)
- NAR Correspondence with John D. Rockefeller Jr., 1948-1949 (Box 34, Folder 400)
- NAR Correspondence with John D. Rockefeller Jr., 1950-1951 (Box 34, Folder 401)
- NAR Correspondence with John D. Rockefeller Jr., 1952-1954 (Box 34, Folder 402)
- NAR Correspondence with John D. Rockefeller Jr., 1952-1954 (Box 34, Folder 0402A)
- NAR Correspondence with John D. Rockefeller Jr., 1955-1956 (Box 34, Folder 403)
- NAR Correspondence with John D. Rockefeller Jr., 1955-1956 (Box 34, Folder 0403A)
- NAR Correspondence with John D. Rockefeller Jr., 1957-1960 (Box 34, Folder 404)
- NAR Correspondence with John D. Rockefeller Jr., 1957-1960 (Box 34, Folder 0404A)
- Correspondence on Fosdick's Biography of John D. Rockefeller Jr. (Box 35, Folder 405)
- NAR Gifts from John D. Rockefeller Jr., 1924-1952 (Box 35, Folder 406)
- NAR Gifts from John D. Rockefeller Jr., 1924-1952 (Box 35, Folder 0406A)
- Correspondence with John D. Rockefeller Jr. on International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC), 1947-1950 (Box 35, Folder 407)
- Correspondence with John D. Rockefeller Jr. on Museum of Modern Art (MoMA) Endowment Gift, 1947-1950 (Box 35, Folder 408)
- John D. Rockefeller Jr. Death - Resolutions, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 409)
- John D. Rockefeller Jr. Death Resolutions, Correspondence and Originals, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 410)
- John D. Rockefeller Jr. Proposed Memorials and Contributions, 1960-1961 (Box 35, Folder 411)
- John D. Rockefeller Jr. Proposed Memorials (Box 35, Folder 412)
- John D. Rockefeller Jr. Memorial Sculpture, 1960-1961 (Box 35, Folder 413)
- John D. Rockefeller Jr. 's Death - General Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 35, Folder 414)
- John D. Rockefeller Jr. 's Death - General Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 35, Folder 0414A)
- John D. Rockefeller Jr. 's Death - Clippings (Box 35, Folder 415)
- John D. Rockefeller Jr. Estate Matters, 1960-1965 (Box 36, Folder 416)
- John D. Rockefeller Jr. Estate Matters, 1960-1965 (Box 36, Folder 0416A)
- John D. Rockefeller Jr. Estate - Kykuit Distribution (Box 36, Folder 417)
- John D. Rockefeller Jr. Estate - Claims, 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 418)
- John D. Rockefeller Jr. Estate - Office Furnishings (Box 36, Folder 419)
- John D. Rockefeller Jr. Condolence Letters
  - List of Letters Received by NAR (Box 36, Folder 420)
  - A (Box 36, Folder 421)
  - Ba-Bi (Box 36, Folder 422)
  - Bl-By (Box 36, Folder 423)
  - Ca-Cl (Box 36, Folder 424)
  - Co-Cu (Box 37, Folder 425)
  - D (Box 37, Folder 426)
  - E (Box 37, Folder 427)
  - F (Box 37, Folder 428)
  - Ga-Go (Box 37, Folder 429)
  - Gr-Gy (Box 37, Folder 430)
  - Ha (Box 38, Folder 431)
  - He-Hy (Box 38, Folder 432)
  - I-J (Box 38, Folder 433)
  - K (Box 38, Folder 434)
  - L (Box 38, Folder 435)
  - Ma (Box 39, Folder 436)
  - Mac and Mc (Box 39, Folder 437)
  - Me (Box 39, Folder 438)
  - Mi (Box 39, Folder 439)
  - Mo-Mu (Box 39, Folder 440)
  - N (Box 39, Folder 441)
  - O (Box 39, Folder 442)
  - Pa-Ph (Box 39, Folder 443)
  - Pi-Pu (Box 39, Folder 444)
  - Q (Box 40, Folder 445)
  - Ra-Ri (Box 40, Folder 446)
  - Ro-Ry (Box 40, Folder 447)
  - Sa-Se (Box 40, Folder 448)
  - Sh-Sm (Box 40, Folder 449)
  - So-Su (Box 40, Folder 450)
  - T (Box 40, Folder 451)
  - U-V (Box 41, Folder 452)
  - Wa-Wh (Box 41, Folder 453)
  - Wi-Wy (Box 41, Folder 454)
  - Y-Z (Box 41, Folder 455)
  - Unsorted (Box 41, Folder 456)
  - Unsorted (Box 41, Folder 457)
  - Unsorted (Box 41, Folder 458)
  - Unsorted (Box 42, Folder 459)
  - Unsorted (Box 42, Folder 460)
- Abby Aldrich Rockefeller
  - Death - General Correspondence, 1948-1970 (Box 42, Folder 461)
  - Folk Art Collection in Williamsburg, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 462)
  - Reprints of Letter to Sons on "Treatment of Minorities" (Box 42, Folder 463)
  - Book - "Letters to Her Sister Lucy" (Box 42, Folder 464)
  - Biography by Mary Ellen Chase (Box 42, Folder 465)
  - Biography by Mary Ellen Chase (Box 42, Folder 0465A)
  - Estate - Meeting, August 29, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 466)
  - Estate - Meeting, August 29, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 0466A)
  - Estate - Meeting, August 29, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 467)
  - Estate - Meeting, August 29, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 0467A)
  - Estate - Seal Harbor Items (Box 42, Folder 468)
  - Estate - Seal Harbor Items (Box 42, Folder 0468A)
  - Estate - 740 Park Avenue Items (Box 43, Folder 469)
  - Estate - Appraisals (Box 43, Folder 470)
  - Estate - Appraisals and Distribution, 1960 (Box 43, Folder 471)
  - Estate - Appraisal for Maine, 1948 (Box 43, Folder 472)
  - Estate - Photo Inventory (Box 44, Folder 473)
  - Estate - Memorial Window, Union Church, 1949-1950 (Box 44, Folder 474)
  - Death - General Correspondence, 1948-1951 (Box 44, Folder 475)
  - Death - List of Condolences, 1948 (Box 44, Folder 476)
  - Condolence Letters (A) (Box 44, Folder 477)
  - Condolence Letters (B) (Box 44, Folder 478)
  - Condolence Letters (C) (Box 44, Folder 479)
    Scope and Contents note
    Includes condolence letter from Marc Chagall
  - Condolence Letters (D) (Box 44, Folder 480)
  - Condolence Letters (E-F) (Box 44, Folder 481)
  - Condolence Letters (G) (Box 45, Folder 482)
  - Condolence Letters (H) (Box 45, Folder 483)
  - Condolence Letters (I-J) (Box 45, Folder 484)
  - Condolence Letters (K-L) (Box 45, Folder 485)
  - Condolence Letters (M) (Box 45, Folder 486)
  - Condolence Letters (N-O) (Box 45, Folder 487)
  - Condolence Letters (P-Q) (Box 45, Folder 488)
  - Condolence Letters (R) (Box 45, Folder 489)
  - Condolence Letters (S) (Box 45, Folder 490)
  - Condolence Letters (T) (Box 45, Folder 491)
  - Condolence Letters (U-V) (Box 45, Folder 492)
  - Condolence Letters (W) (Box 45, Folder 493)
  - Condolence Letters (X-Z) (Box 45, Folder 494)
- Martha Baird Rockefeller - General, 1951-1971 (Box 46, Folder 495)
- Martha Baird Rockefeller - Union Church Memorial Service, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 496)
- Martha Baird Rockefeller Condolences, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 497)
- Martha Baird Rockefeller Estate, 1971-1972 (Box 46, Folder 498)
- Abby Rockefeller Mauze - General, 1946-1971 (Box 46, Folder 499)
- John D. Rockefeller 3rd - General, 1931-1971 (Box 46, Folder 500)
- John D. Rockefeller 3rd - Trip to Asia, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 501)
- John D. Rockefeller 3rd - The John D. Rockefeller 3rd Fund (Box 46, Folder 502)
- Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller (Mrs. John D. Rockefeller 3rd), 1952-1968 (Box 46, Folder 503)
- Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller (Mrs. John D. Rockefeller 3rd), 1952-1968 (Box 46, Folder 0503A)
- Laurance Spelman Rockefeller
  - 1920-1955 (Box 47, Folder 507)
  - 1920-1955 (Box 47, Folder 0507A)
  - 1956-1971 (Box 47, Folder 508)
  - 1956-1971 (Box 47, Folder 0508A)
  - Book on Conservation (Box 47, Folder 510)
- Mary French Rockefeller (Mrs. Laurance S. Rockefeller) (Box 47, Folder 511)
- Winthrop Rockefeller
  - Estate (Box 48, Folder 516)
  - General, 1941-1971 (Box 48, Folder 517)
  - Williamsburg, Virginia (Box 48, Folder 518)
  - Arkansas (Box 48, Folder 519)
  - Arkansas Politics (Box 48, Folder 520)
  - Annual Cattle Sales (Box 48, Folder 521)
  - Cattle Sales Brochures (Box 48, Folder 522)
- Winthrop Paul Rockefeller (Box 49, Folder 523)
- Jeannette Edris Rockefeller (Mrs. Winthrop Rockefeller) (Box 49, Folder 524)
- Margaret McGrath Rockefeller (Mrs. David Rockefeller) (Box 49, Folder 532)
- David Rockefeller - General, 1942-1958 (Box 49, Folder 525)
- NAR Requests for Information, 1961-1965 (Box 50, Folder 534)
- David Rockefeller - General, 1959-1972 (Box 49, Folder 526)
- NAR General Correspondence, 1921-1929 (Box 50, Folder 535)
- David Rockefeller - General, 1959-1972 (Box 49, Folder 526a)
  Conditions Governing Access
- NAR General Correspondence, 1930-1933 (Box 50, Folder 536)
- David Rockefeller - Boats in Maine, 1946-1971 (Box 49, Folder 527)
- NAR General Correspondence, 1934 (Box 50, Folder 537)
- David Rockefeller - from Albany, 1959-1968 (Box 49, Folder 528)
- NAR General Correspondence, 1935 (Box 50, Folder 538)
- David Rockefeller - Latin America Trips, 1948; 1950 (Box 49, Folder 529)
- NAR General Correspondence, 1936 (Box 50, Folder 539)
- David Rockefeller - Embarcadero Project, 1967-1968 (Box 49, Folder 530)
- NAR General Correspondence, 1937 (Box 51, Folder 540)
- NAR General Correspondence, 1938 (Box 51, Folder 541)
- NAR General Correspondence, 1939 (Box 51, Folder 542)
- NAR General Correspondence, 1940 (Box 51, Folder 543)
- NAR General Correspondence, 1941 (Box 51, Folder 544)
- NAR General Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 52, Folder 545)
- NAR General Correspondence, 1946 (Box 52, Folder 546)
- NAR General Correspondence, 1947-1955 (Box 52, Folder 547)
- NAR General Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 52, Folder 548)
- NAR General Correspondence, 1958-1961 (Box 52, Folder 549)
- NAR General Correspondence (A-Z), 1934-1965 (Box 53, Folder 550)
- NAR Passports and ID Cards During World War II (Box 53, Folder 551)
- NAR General, 1943-1949 (Box 53, Folder 552)
- NAR General, 1943-1949 (Box 53, Folder 0552A)
- NAR General, 1950-1958 (Box 53, Folder 553)
- NAR General, 1950-1958 (Box 53, Folder 0553A)
- NAR General, 1959-1971 (Box 53, Folder 554)
- NAR General, 1959-1971 (Box 53, Folder 0554A)
- NAR Campaign Publications, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 555)
- NAR Appointment Books, 1962 and 1963 (Box 54, Folder 556)
- NAR Appointment Book, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 557)
- NAR Appointment Books, 1966 and 1967 (Box 54, Folder 558)
- NAR Miscellaneous Bank Accounts, 1956-1957 (Box 54, Folder 559)
- NAR Birthday Greetings, 1948-1965 (Box 54, Folder 560)
- NAR Birthday Greetings, 1948-1965 (Box 54, Folder 0560A)
- Miscellaneous Cash Accounts, 1959-1970 (Box 54, Folder 561)
- NAR Clippings, 1938-1971 (Box 55, Folder 562)
- NAR Clothing Orders, 1939-1971 (Box 55, Folder 563)
- NAR College Expenses and Arrangements, 1926-1931 (Box 55, Folder 564)
- Conflict of Interest Memos, 1953-1958 (Box 55, Folder 565)
- NAR Diet Guidelines, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 566)
- NAR Expense Book, 1920-1923 (Box 55, Folder 567)
- NAR Expense Book, 1924-1928 (Box 55, Folder 568)
- NAR Expense Book, 1929-1931 (Box 55, Folder 569)
- NAR Guns and Permits, Licenses (Box 55, Folder 570)
- NAR Biographical Information, 1929-1969 (Box 55, Folder 571)
- "Rockefeller Letter" Issue, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 572)
- Letters, Complimentary, 1945-1964 (Box 55, Folder 573)
- NAR Medical, 1938-1971 (Box 55, Folder 574)
- NAR Medical, 1938-1971 (Box 55, Folder 0574A)
- NAR Dental, 1942-1960 (Box 55, Folder 575)
- NAR Hay Fever, 1942-1953 (Box 55, Folder 576)
- Memoranda and Reminders, 1932, 1952-1970 (Box 56, Folder 577)
- Memoranda and Reminders, 1932, 1952-1970 (Box 56, Folder 0577A)
- NAR Oral History from Columbia University, 1951-1966 (Box 56, Folder 578)
- NAR Personal Data (Box 56, Folder 579)
- NAR Personal Data (Box 56, Folder 0579A)
- NAR Personal - Appointments and Awards (Box 56, Folder 580)
- NAR Personal - Contributions (Box 56, Folder 581)
- NAR Personal - J. A. Morris Biography (Box 56, Folder 582)
- NAR Phone Calls and Memos, 1957-1958 (Box 56, Folder 583)
- NAR Possessions and Inventories, 1960-1971 (Box 56, Folder 584)
- NAR Possessions and Inventories, 1960-1971 (Box 56, Folder 0584A)
- NAR Powers of Attorney, 1958 and 1963 (Box 56, Folder 585)
- NAR Purchases - Bills Paid, 1930-1971 (Box 57, Folder 586)
- NAR Purchases - Bills Paid, 1930-1971 (Box 57, Folder 0586A)
- NAR Purchases - Butler of Madrid, 1964-1968 (Box 57, Folder 587)
- NAR School Reports and Programs, 1918-1930 (Box 57, Folder 588)
- NAR Security Clearances (Box 57, Folder 589)
- NAR Security Clearances (Box 57, Folder 0589A)
- NAR Signature, Use of (Box 57, Folder 590)
- NAR Speeches, Miscellaneous, 1936-1970 (Box 57, Folder 591)
- NAR Speeches, Correspondence, Lists, 1932-1970 (Box 58, Folder 592)
- NAR Public Statements, 1958-1968 (Box 58, Folder 593)
- Stamps, First Day Covers, Etc. (Box 58, Folder 594)
- NAR Tax-Related Correspondence, 1942-1971 (Box 58, Folder 595)
- NAR as Trustee for Trusts Created by John D. Rockefeller Sr. (Box 58, Folder 599)
- U.S. Government - Notice of Personal Appointments (Box 58, Folder 600)
- Washington, DC, 1948-1960 (Box 58, Folder 601)
- Washington, DC - Planning Board, 1958 (Box 58, Folder 602)
- NAR Will Correspondence, 1934-1968 (Box 58, Folder 603)
- NAR Will Correspondence, 1934-1968 (Box 58, Folder 0603A)